https://www.wilkinson.co.uk/privacy/

Please wait...
Cameras
Compact Digital CamerasCSC / MirrorlessDSLRRangefinderNature / Tough / Waterproof360° CamerasInstant Cameras & Instant Film
Lenses
DSLR LensesCSC / Mirrorless LensesManual LensesCine LensesLens AccessoriesFilters
Accessories
Memory CardsBatteries & ChargersGripsFilmCamera CareCablesFrames and Albums
Video
CamcordersProfessional VideoAction Video CamerasMonitors & RecordersTripods, Supports & RigsSound & LightCine LensesGimbals
Lighting & Studio
FlashgunsLED LightingStudio & Location LightingBackgrounds & StandsLight ModifiersTriggers / Transmitters / MetersLighting Accessories
Tripods & Support
TripodsTripod HeadsMonopodsAccessoriesGimbals
Bags & Straps
Pouches and CasesShoulder BagsBackpacksRoller BagsBag AccessoriesCamera Straps
Binoculars & Scopes
BinocularsSpotting ScopesAstro Telescopes
Computing
Printers & ScannersPapers & InksMonitorsColour ManagementSoftwareStorageGraphics Tablets
Working From Home
GimbalsTripods / Stands / SupportsLightsMicrophonesAudio RecordersAccessories
Home
ProductsView All ProductsCamerasView All CamerasCompact Digital CamerasCSC / MirrorlessDSLRRangefinderNature / Tough / Waterproof360° CamerasInstant Cameras & Instant FilmView All Instant Cameras & Instant FilmInstant CamerasInstant FilmInstant PrintersLensesView All LensesDSLR LensesCSC / Mirrorless LensesManual LensesCine LensesLens AccessoriesView All Lens AccessoriesLens AdaptersExtension TubesTeleconvertersLens Caps & HoodsFiltersView All FiltersUV / Protective FiltersCircular Polarising FiltersNeutral Density FiltersClose Up FiltersVariable DensityLEE FiltersFormatt-HitechCokin Creative FiltersFilter AccessoriesAccessoriesView All AccessoriesMemory CardsBatteries & ChargersGripsFilmCamera CareCablesFrames and Albums View All Frames and Albums AlbumsFramesVideoView All VideoCamcordersProfessional VideoAction Video CamerasMonitors & RecordersTripods, Supports & RigsSound & LightCine LensesGimbalsLighting & StudioView All Lighting & StudioFlashgunsLED LightingStudio & Location LightingBackgrounds & StandsLight ModifiersTriggers / Transmitters / MetersLighting AccessoriesTripods & SupportView All Tripods & SupportTripodsTripod HeadsMonopodsAccessoriesGimbalsBags & StrapsView All Bags & StrapsPouches and CasesShoulder BagsBackpacksRoller BagsBag AccessoriesCamera StrapsBinoculars & ScopesView All Binoculars & ScopesBinocularsView All BinocularsCompact BinocularsFull size BinocularsMonocularsBinocular Straps & AccessoriesSpotting ScopesAstro TelescopesComputingView All ComputingPrinters & ScannersPapers & InksView All Papers & InksInksPaperCompact Photo Printer PacksMonitorsColour ManagementView All Colour ManagementMonitor CalibrationSoftwareStorageView All StorageSSDMini DV & VHS-CCD-R / DVD-RMass StorageUSB Pen DrivesCard ReadersMicro SDCompact Flash CardsSD CardsCFast & XQDGraphics TabletsWorking From HomeView All Working From HomeGimbalsTripods / Stands / SupportsLightsMicrophonesAudio RecordersAccessoriesGift VouchersWhat's NewPre-ownedView All Pre-ownedPre-owned CanonPre-owned NikonPre-owned SonyPre-owned OlympusPre-owned TamronPre-owned LeicaPre-owned FujifilmPre-owned SigmaPre-owned PentaxPre-owned PanasonicBrandsView All BrandsCanonView All CanonCanon EOS R MirrorlessView All Canon EOS R MirrorlessEOS R CamerasRF LensesLens AdaptersCanon CamerasCanon LensesCanon PrintersCanon VideoCanon Paper & InksCanon LightingCanon BinocularsCanon AccessoriesNikonView All NikonNikon CamerasNikon LensesNikon LightingPanasonicView All PanasonicLumix SView All Lumix SLumix S CamerasLumix S LensesSonyManfrottoFujifilmOlympusLeicaBillinghamLoweproSigma3 Legged ThingAnsmannArtisan & ArtistAtomosBlack RapidCamlinkCelestronCokinDJIElinchromEnergizerEpsonFotospeedGitzoGoProHahnelHamaHasselbladHawkeKenroLastoliteLee FiltersLeofotoMagModMindShift GearPeak DesignPentaxPolaroid OriginalsProfotoRØDERotolightSamyangSandiskSennheiserSwarovskiTamronThink Tank PhotoZEISSZhiyunLomographyView All LomographyCamerasFilmKONO!Studio HireView All Studio HireAbout the studioFacilitiesBooking, Rates & Terms
Skills & Workshops
In-store Workshops
Liverpool Learning Suite
Books
Stores
Contact
Blog
Prints & Gifts
Privacy
Wilkinson Cameras is the trading name of Frank Wilkinson Cameras Ltd. and also includes Digital Splash (www.digitalsplash.tv) and WeBuyAnyCamera (webuyanycamera.com). This privacy policy explains how we use any personal information we collect about you when use this website.
Wilkinson Cameras (and our related brands) collects personal information when you register with us, place an order with us for products or services and when contacting us using online forms, questions or Live Help.
We use the information provided to provide the services or goods requested, maintain guarantee/warranty records or to provide the information you have requested.
Unless you choose to accept marketing emails, by signing up to our online newsletter or by ticking the relevant box at the checkout, we will only contact you in relation to your order or enquiry placed. We do not share with or sell your information to 3rd parties for marketing purposes.Should you choose to accept marketing emails, you can unsubscribe or change your preferences at any time.
Your privacy is very important to us and we promise to look after your information, keep it safe and only use it in the ways outlined in our Privacy Policy. Our Information Commissioner’s Office Registration number is ZA280581.
Topics covered:
What information we collect about you
How we use this information
Marketing
Access to your information, correction and data retention
Cookies
Other websites
Changes to our privacy policy
How to contact us
Full Privacy Policy Document
What information we collect about you:
We collect information about you when you register with us or place an order for products or services. We also collect information when you voluntarily complete customer surveys, provide feedback, contact us or fill in an online form and participate in competitions. Website usage information is collected using cookies.
How we use this information
We collect information about you to process your order, manage your account, reply to your enquiries and, if you agree, to email you about other products and services we think may be of interest to you.
We will also use some information provided to analyse and improve our website, products or user experience, including personalising your future visits to the website.
Order data will be used to process your order and some information will be shared with our service providers, for example to ask you to review your product or service.
Marketing
If you have agreed to be contacted for marketing purposes, then we may share your data with other brands within Frank Wilkinson Cameras Ltd., which includes Digital Splash and WeBuyAnyCamera.We will never share your information for marketing purposes with any 3rd party company.You can change your marketing preferences or unsubscribe from marketing emails at any time, by contacting us or by simply using the “Change preferences” or “Unsubscribe” options on any marketing emails we send to you. These are on the bottom of every marketing email.
Access to your information, correction and data retention
You have the right to request a copy of the information that we hold about you. If you would like a copy of some or all of your personal information, please emailor write to us at the address below (see the “How to Contact Us” section). We will provide this free of charge once. Subsequent requests will have a small charge.
We want to make sure that your personal information is accurate and up to date. You may ask us to correct or remove information you think is inaccurate.
We will aim to provide this information or complete any changes within a reasonable timeframe.
We will retain your personal data for the period necessary to fulfil the purposes outlined in this Privacy Notice and our complete Privacy Policy.In some cases we may need to keep your data for longer periods in order to fulfil our legal obligations.
We won’t keep your data for longer than is deemed necessary.
Cookies
Our website uses cookies, as almost all websites do, to help provide you with the best experience we can. Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer or mobile phone when you browse websites.
Our cookies help us:• Make our website work as you'd expect• Save you having to login every time you visit the site• Remember your settings during and between visits• Improve the speed/security of the site• Allow you to share pages with social networks like Facebook• Continuously improve our website for you• Make our marketing more efficient (ultimately helping us to offer the service we do at the price we do)
We do not use cookies to:• Collect any personally identifiable information (without your express permission)• Collect any sensitive information (without your express permission)• Pass personally identifiable data to third parties
Other websites
Our website contains links to other websites. This privacy policy only applies to this website so when you link to other websites you should read their own privacy policies.
Changes to our privacy policy
We keep our privacy policy under regular review and we will place any updates on this web page. This privacy policy was last updated on 23rd May 2018.
How to contact us
Please contact us if you have any question s about our privacy policy or information we hold about you:
By Email:
https://www.wilkinson.co.uk/w/contact-us/
In Writing:
Wilkinson Cameras25 Charnley Fold,Bamber Bridge,Preston,PR5 6PS
Full Privacy Policy Document
This Privacy Notice summarises our full Privacy Policy. The full Privacy Policy goes into a lot more detail. We have tried to cover everything, whilst still keeping it simple. If you have any questions or concerns, then please get in touch and we’ll be glad to assist you.
To View our Full Privacy Policy - Click here
01772 252188
EMAIL US
YOUR LOCAL STORE
LIVE HELP
Sign up to our newsletter for the latest News, offers and events. We never share your details with anyone else.
Please fill in the email box and click the sign up button to receive our newsletter
This websites use cookies. By continuing to browse the site you are agreeing to our use of cookies.
Accept
More information
